

Ali Taee Front-End Developer

Front-end Developer with 5+ years of experience building responsive websites to web applications. I enjoy every aspect of the job from the user interface implementation to advanced JavaScript topics. I always passion to learn more and improve my work. I enjoy working on pure projects using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript as much as working on front-end libraries and frameworks like React.

Contacts

- Ali.Taee.72@gmail.com
- in Linkedin
- **Stack overflow**
- Github

Skills



Languages

Persian (Native) English

Experiences

Front-end Developer

Snappfood - Tehran, Iran

Feb 2021 - Present

Snappfood is the largest online food ordering and grocery shopping platform in Iran

- Worked in a team closely with designers, developers, QA engineers, scrum masters, and product managers using Scrum.
- Created a document for onboarding new developers.
- Developed new features for the mobile and desktop applications.

Tools and Technologies: HTML, CSS, SCSS, Styled components, BEM, JavaScript, ES6+, TypeScript, React, React Router, Redux, Redux-Saga, Next.js, Storybook, Webpack, Babel, ESlint, Prettier, Git and GitLab

Front-end Developer

Rasa Labs - Tehran, Iran

Dec 2019 - Jan 2021

Rasa Labs provide CCTV systems and Parental control systems.

- Created dashboards for our internal projects using React.
- Created common components to reuse in our projects.
- Worked in a team closely with designers, developers, product owners
- Maintained large legacy codes in old projects and refactor them for better performance and fixing bugs.

Tools and Technologies: HTML, CSS, SCSS, JSS, BEM, JavaScript, ES6+, React, React Router, Redux, Material-UI, react-i18next, Socket.IO, ESlint, Prettier, Git and GitLab

Front-end Developer / WordPress Developer

Nabzino - Tehran, Iran

Feb 2019 - Aug 2019

Nabzino is a digital marketing agency.

- Created dashboard for one of our internal projects using React.
- Converted UI landing design into WordPress page.
- Developed a game campaign with a team of developers and designers in tight deadline, in which the users had to enter their phone numbers and names, and then choose among their favorite game characters. The winner was chosen in a lottery based on their scores. This project was done using Vue.js.
- Created WordPress shortcut posts plugins and video gallery plugins.

Tools and Technologies: HTML, CSS, SCSS, JSS, BEM, JavaScript, ES6+, React, Vue, Redux, Material-UI, react-i18next, WordPress, PHP, WordPress Plugin Development, Git and GitLab, Bitbucket

Arta Seo - Esfahan, Iran

Mar 2018 - Feb 2019

Arta Seo is a website development company and digital marketing agency.

- Converted UI designs into WordPress website.
- Helped interns to learn HTML, CSS, and WordPress.
- Introduced WordPress plugin development to the company.
- Created a WordPress plugin for a client. This plugin allows to enter the buildings' info such as floors, area, location, image gallery and etc, to show the buildings to the customers.

Tools and Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, WordPress, WooCommerce, PHP, WordPress Plugin Development, ACF, Custom Post Types

WordPress Developer / Website Manager

Asr-e Digital - Esfahan, Iran

2014 - 2017

Asr-e Digital is an online e-commerce.

- Website management.
- Content editing.
- WordPress Development for blog website.

Tools and Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, WordPress

Education

Safahan

Associate's degree - Computer Software Engineering

2014 - 2017